// src/data/obscureLandmarks.js
export default [
  { front: "Victoria Falls", back: "Zambia" },
  { front: "Mount Roraima", back: "Venezuela" },
  { front: "Göbekli Tepe", back: "Turkey" },
  { front: "Lake Baikal", back: "Russia" },
  { front: "Tiger’s Nest Monastery", back: "Bhutan" },
  { front: "Salar de Uyuni", back: "Bolivia" },
  { front: "Ha Long Bay", back: "Vietnam" },
  { front: "Sigiriya Rock", back: "Sri Lanka" },
  { front: "Neuschwanstein Castle", back: "Germany" },
  { front: "Plitvice Lakes", back: "Croatia" },
  { front: "Giant’s Causeway", back: "Northern Ireland" },
  { front: "Mount Sinai", back: "Egypt" },
];
